ERIKA VERKAAIK 3D GAME ARTIST

<u>erikaverkaaik@gmail.com</u> erikaverkaaik.com

0420 327 521

INTRODUCTION

During my study I was continuously involved in small student game projects and learnt a lot about working with game designers, working to deadlines and creating assets that suit the tone and function of the game. I continuously push myself to research, learn and incorporate modern work practices, pipelines and software into my work. I am extremely passionate about games and aim to create rich and engaging worlds through my games and art.

SKILLS

ASSET CREATION:

- 3D modelling
- 3D animation
- Texturing (both hand-painting and using PBR software)
- Importing and integrating into game engine

ART AND DESIGN:

- Determining art direction
- Creation of art bible for team
- Concept and design

SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

Adobe Photoshop	Expert knowledge - four years of professional experience
Autodesk 3DsMax	Good knowledge
Unreal Engine	Good knowledge
Unity	Good knowledge
SourceTree	Good knowledge
Quixel Suite	Intermediate knowledge
Substance Painter	Currently learning

EXPERIENCE

Frances Suter Photography - Editor and Assistant

JULY 2011 - PRESENT

- Portrait photography
- Processing photographs digitally in preparation for commercial sale
- Social media management
- Basic marketing work
- Designing album and photobook layouts

Euclideon - Art Intern

MAY 2015 - JUNE 2015

- Software Quality Assurance
- Creation of 2D and 3D art assets
- Database work.

EDUCATION

SAE QANTM, Brisbane - Bachelor of Animation

JAN 2014 - AUG 2016

• Final GPA = 6.08

REFEREES

Frances Suter

MANAGER

0414 339 543

Nathan Wentworth-Perry

SUPERVISOR

0431 675 553